The deformed C4 plane is
At that time we stole
I'm sure it's a bomb.
I know, I know, I know
I'm watching it now!
Just one word...
Am I ours now?
Are you asking?
Why is that thing moving around now?
Have you checked the remaining supplies in the military?
Ah, yes
This item is not currently used by the military.
What I worked on at that time
Processed for operational use
I exported it.
So, obviously then
You sent it all overseas.
But the items that went abroad
How do I make a U-turn and come back in?
Maybe in the middle
Could it be that there was a delivery accident?
The deposit was completed at that time.
Then it wasn’t a delivery accident.
Maybe this
Shouldn’t it be seen as terrorism?
In terms of terrorism
Well, there is a statement
what are your requirements
It shouldn't be there!
And Kiyunxi, nigga
Why are you terrorizing?!
I don't know if it's Seoul
Ah, stuffy bastard, this is Mr.
Let's gather together
Hey, anyway
The kids who went to the field this time
Control your mouth properly
Manage it properly
If this goes wrong this time
We're all going to die
Got it?
kids on vacation
Everyone, please come in.
Okay
cyber operations command
Logistics Support Group Leader
Director of the Defense Acquisition Program Administration?
Why are they all coming out of there at once?
Do you know me?
What kind of unit is this?
uncle
Is that JDD?
JDD Special Operations Forces?
Wow, this is my first time hearing it.
Hey, you know, why
Jindo dog alarm control...
Huh? Look here
What are you looking at?
Look here
'New day'
'It's coming'?
Uh, is it turned off?
Why is this happening?
Hey, what happened to this?
It's really off
Why is this happening?
Did you do something wrong?
Oh, well, anyway, huh?
‘A new day is coming’? This, this
What on earth is this?
how do i know
Just read what you see
I know how to read too
So what I asked was...
Doyeon's father
Oh, change your clothes first.
yes, thank you
Well, are you really okay?
I'm just hurt inside
Isn't it like that?
Uh, I'm fine...
Oh, don't come.
no, that's not it
What happened to us too?
Need to check...
What is it?
I'm sure he died
Did you just clean it up?
Does the clean team work together?
what?
There's no one there?
Are you sure you really fought? uh?
For no reason, I just sprinkled red pepper powder on it.
Soaked in ketchup like this
Well, isn’t it like that?
Eat it, eat it
Eat it, eat it, eh?
what am i
Doesn't that seem like a good thing to do?
wow!
- why?
It's so clean
Brother, I'm here
I've never seen it this clean before.
Wow!
Hey, sure
Huh? Mr. Lee
These people are real
There were cameras in the hallway and entrance.
Where do you see that?
Ah, that...
Management office?
That's strange
Is the capacity full? Why is it only empty here?
Hey
Do you think someone touched this?
I would have gotten rid of everything.
So quickly?
No, I also clean the bathroom.
They even took care of the CCTV?
These guys are pros
clean team
I think we move together
Clean team?
The kids who clean up after that?
Ha, Mr.
When I was talking about being a spy or something.
I should have taken my step away
Let's start by reporting it to the police.
What are you reporting?
I went to poop
You beat someone until they bled?
But if you don't want to use dumbang later,
I have to leave a record
That's right
Hey Yonghee
Then contact Police Officer Park.
no
Please call 112
No personal records
yes
But what...
They say they fought while pooping?
Hey, Mr.
Take out the shit
Then why did you go to the bathroom?
What if you ask?
Well, let’s talk about JDD.
Well, is this a real unit?
Really in our country
Is there such a unit?
So
No comment
Oh, I can’t speak?
So you’re saying it exists?
JDD
Is it really an abbreviation for Jindo dog?
No comment
They say it is only used for special killing operations.
and
Even within the military
I didn't know that unit existed.
It's
I heard you are not part of the Ministry of National Defense.
Well, is that even real?
Awesome, really, wow
What the hell is that
Where did you pick it all up? uh?
state secrets
Just talking randomly
Because no comment
Please no comment from now on.
yes, that's right
Well, that, something like that.
Oh, how are you going to do that?
- What are you going to do?
- yes?
Oh, this?
Earlier, I was wondering whether I should talk about it or not.
I missed the timing
Even if I pass it over
Please check the information inside and give it to me.
And the black box video of the intersection accident
Please give me a copy
Hey, that would be great, you can do it, right?
No, this was earlier
come in remotely
The settings were reset
I'll give it a try
Today I set up the equipment first.
Then I'll leave
Ah, yes
yes please go in
Doyeon’s father!
- Yes
- Uh, come in... yo.
Hey
It was really JDD
Hey, so is the gun thing.
Now it fits perfectly
It's Korea's Jason Bourne, awesome
Hey, I mean
Better than we thought
He's a much scarier person.
They recognize me right away too.
‘The strongest’
'You made things difficult'
- Brother
- Uh
Isn't this actually a good thing for us?
Do-yeon has the same father.
Are you having a sports day?
What's your side, Mr.
Hey, but definitely
I don’t think you’re on that side, right?
Oh, of course
Brother, now
Stop doubting yourself!
What are you doing with the computer?
Hacking, what can I do?
all night long
Pop, pop, pop, huh?
Just before, huh?
'Oh my, how can I do this...'
Oh my
You are like that, huh?
uh? suddenly
coming in remotely
This is your first computer, huh?
I was embarrassed!
Oh my, what the hell
Are you embarrassed?
- Brother
-Why?
I'll figure this out
My brother takes it.
Even the kids in the dojang for no reason
What if it gets dangerous?
The kids can't do it, but I can?
give it
Me and my brother
Why?
In the future, Doyeon’s father too
Call me at the hardware store.
This idiot, wow, really
Oh my, oh my, really, Mr.
Okay
go
Well, I'm there too, bro.
Oh, right, come to work.
Honey, what are you doing there?
After going to the bathroom
Are you coming now?
Uh, I took a walk around the neighborhood.
Go in and sleep
‘Force stamp’?
Take off your clothes straight away
Don't turn it over
Okay, hurry up and go to sleep.
Are you foreign?
It's dangerous!
Who sent it? tell me
‘A new day is coming’?
Kim Min-seo, do you really want to do this?
no
Among my close friends, I am the only one who doesn't have one.
me forward
I'm going to study really hard
Just buy me one of these, okay?
Ah, mom
Hey, hey, come to your senses
What is a middle school student
Wearing 500,000 won sneakers, huh?
Hey, your dad is working so hard
Mom, can’t you see she’s having such a hard time?
Listen to this
no, mom
Wow, you are like that
Even if I don’t call you out loud
I am Kim Min-seo’s mother
Everyone in the neighborhood knows
Oh, are you really not going to buy it?
uh
You earn money to buy it
It's too much
Wow, that's too much
Did you adopt me?
Does anyone adopt?
You have to have money
Wow
- Hello
- Oh, is Myung-oh here?
What's wrong with Minseo?
What is butane gas?
Ah, there
Butane gas exploded in the ATM
I'm going to collect everything.
Hey
Are you going to work soon?
That's right
You got a job at a large company
Your mother's mouth was caught in your ear.
They say they give a shot to the women’s club ladies.
Mom too
Hey, why?
I, Minseo Kim, am going to Korea University like you.
You get a job at a large company, right?
I just slaughter cows and pigs
Just, huh?
A local village feast while dancing to the sesame seeds
I'm going to do it, ugh.
My daughter, huh?
I won't buy you sneakers
Saying “I’m not your real mother”, oh my gosh
Minseo is smart.
Jeonghwan says that
Good understanding too
He said he was following along well in class.
Jeonghwan doesn’t say empty words.
Oh, really?
Sure
Anyway
For introducing me to a good tutor
thank you so much
Don't say anything
- I'll go now.
- Yeah.
- Goodbye.
- Go, good work.
yes
Actually
It's hard to be stupid if you look like me
Yeah
Is it beyond your expectations?
The basics will be over soon
Minseo, with this good hair
Why haven't you studied yet?
You said you did well, but why is your expression like that?
Sullivan said his life was a mess.
They say it’s thanks to my parents.
My biological parents abandoned me
Now my parents gave me everything
I was adopted and lived my second life.
Well, thanks to that, I was successful.
teacher's car
Did you buy it with the money you earned?
No, parents chance.
Ah, my mom told me
I want you to earn and buy your own sneakers.
But
Teacher, do you have a girlfriend?
no
So these days I
Studying is the most fun
No, with this head for so long
I don't know what I did when I didn't study
Shall we solve the next problem?
okay
pen
honey
Did you change your clothes?
Where are you going again?
Ah, the youth president is a blessing.
I'll be back soon
What kind of youth leader?
Oh, the owner of the hardware store is the youth council president.
What kind of young man does that face look like?
Anyway
The super lady next to her is the president of the women’s association.
The owner of the laundromat across the street has a bankbook
What is the neighborhood?
It's a lot more organized than it looks, huh.
I'll go and come back
Because today is dangerous
Don't go out with Doyeon.
Stay home, huh?
What's dangerous?
Fine, fine dust, uh
Ah, fine dust
Oh my, it's so damn underground, uh
It's murderous, uh
I'll go and come back
But why are you leaving?
Why are you leaving?
Now
If it's an attempt to poison
I should have chosen the medicine well.
Because I have a strong tolerance
It doesn't die well from most poisons.
In JDD
Do you also have training to prepare for poisoning?
Where is that training?
Oh my, that’s right, tsk tsk tsk.
IC
Who said what about my tolerance?
Ah, I thought about it before I bought it.
Why didn't you do that?
Are you being kind?
They give me something like this so they get suspicious
And Korean fathers
It's all tolerant
kids spilled food
I picked it up so much that I ate it
It's done
I heard HID came out
Well, there's a reason
Later, I went to the maintenance battalion.
Me too
Let’s ask just one question.
How old is our hardware store manager?
Oh, me?
Class of ’98
Huh? I'm also 98
So, what about the Sheep?
Hey, this...
Same student number
I met you in the neighborhood like this
Oh my friend, nice to meet you
Judging by the way he turns his horse around, he's fast, right?
Are you the zodiac sign of Jannabit?
Who said they changed their words?
That's the one who did the talking, huh?
Chi, that's it, that's it, that's it, uh
Talk to me about JDD.
the army
A mountain I can never go to
Do you know where it is?
Are there any mountains the military cannot go to?
Mt. Baekdu, no, no, no, no
Everest, correct answer
Ah
mi
no
mountain
Amino acid, Uno?
On a topic I don’t know anything about
Whenever you open your mouth, do you talk about the military?
Is it HID? uh?
Where's the gun? I have to shoot it.
Oh my, really, this guy...
Uh, honey
Dad, where are you?
Ah, daughter
Dad came out for a moment.
I'll be in soon
uh
Huge
After dinner
The intersection gun carriage is coming there, huh?
Because I decided to have a drink with my brothers.
If you move to town
Well, you should get to know people and that's it.
Isn't that right, friend?
I have a favor to ask.
Saying no comment in front of people
Let's not bring it up, okay?
Let's do it, friend.
So
Now I'm having fun with my brother
Make your brother feel comfortable too
Yes, I will treat you as my brother.
Oh, draw it
I'm really comfortable already, already
No, I'm in the hospital with a sly smile
Better than when you acted to me
I’m much happier now, hey, huh?
The name is Choi...
- River, river, yes
- river, river
Your face is so sad
The name is completely different again
Strong Boy, Strong
I don't know anything else
I will never lose my name
To be honest, me too
It's a name that appeals to women.
that
Do you know this, ‘Kim Soo-il’s Diamond’?
Namyeon also said that I am as big as this fist.
He said he would buy me a diamond
You just seduced me like that.
Oh my, who is it now?
Do you know Kim Soo-il’s diamond?
And brother
Do you really know how much diamond is worth? uh?
Do you know how much something like this is worth? uh?
Don’t you know how much something like this costs?
Oh my, you braggart.
- One hit with a fist this big...
- Oh my.
Shall I shake off the corn?
Ah, as soon as I moved in
The neighborhood is a mess.
This rarely happens
We are turning this into a special tourist zone.
Even when house prices rise
The atmosphere was very good
How old is our Kang?
Is it similar to our byeongnam?
uh
Same class, huh
friend, friend
Oh, then Jannabi?
Then our river is the same age as me.
I am a sheep
Our sick brother is
Even if it looks very scary
There is a very cute corner
Oh, really
All my friends are sheep
And if we have the same class number, we are friends.
- Right, bro?
- Oh my, yes, yes, yes.
My brother knows that feeling
Come on, have a drink, little brother.
Hey, it's Jannabiti.
Excuse me
Come to think of it, we
This is our first time getting together since that day.
- Right.
- Uh
Jihoon, that’s right.
You were there when the accident happened that day too.
yes
Oh, I was cleaning up the store that day.
I left work when the sun rose.
Were you surprised too?
Oh, I forgot
Enjoy your meal
Oh my, really
Was Byeongnam fast?
Wait a minute
IC
Hey there
By any chance, other than the truck that day
Did you see the driver of the car on the other side?
I don't know the driver of the car on the other side.
As soon as the fire truck put out the fire
A wrecker came
But the wrecker
I just took that car.
Then, is it the color of the wrecker?
Company name...
I don't remember that
What else?
I stayed until dawn
I wonder if I saw something
That's right
And for two and a half bucks
They came separately
the accident scene
They were just cleaning it.
I see you wearing a single military uniform.
They seemed like 5th grade kids.
Two and a half bucks?
2.5 ton army truck?
Yes, that's two and a half dong
I know because I was a driver.
It seemed like a military support group?
At that time, there was flood recovery.
I went to put out a forest fire.
‘What is the fortress?
They also clean up traffic accident scenes.'
Then I saw it
Ah, thank you
Let's go
Are both of you moving?
Why did you crash the car?
uh? what?
Hey, grab your tools, quick.
As soon as the fire truck put out the fire
A wrecker came
But the wrecker
I just took that car.
accident and driving a car
They said they were going towards Hanbalsan Mountain.
With the other vehicle
There's no driver's record.
Alive or dead?
There's no trace at all
The fruit is bigger there.
What is it?
Why is this open?
what?
Are you a frog?
Hey, wrap it up.
"Join Us"
"Connecting"
Wow
What do I do when the power is on?
What do you eat?
Hey, it's ramen at this time.
I like ramen, bro.
Uh, okay, let's eat.
AC
Hey, isn't it on yet?
yes
Hey, what is it, tsk
How many?
Just boil three, three.
Three?
Three for yourself?
yes
The investigation isn't over yet.
Do an autopsy
When was the funeral over?
Isn't it over yet?
We are doing our best too
Lady, it’s frustrating.
The dead brother-in-law is the brother-in-law.
My sister too
I guess I have to live!
The baby's mother just left
My husband was in a car accident at that intersection...
thank you
Come and only buy discounted items.
I bought it
The child is young and won't be able to work.
Of course, I understand.
yes
Deputy Director Choi, has the report been compiled?
Early in the morning on the day of the accident
The soldiers cleared the scene.
An employee at the food stall across the street said he saw it.
soldier? Ah...
If you join the military or government
This is a pain in the ass
Let’s summarize this matter like this.
The death benefit is
I'll post a preliminary decision urgently.
Payment will be made immediately after payment is made.
Oh, no.
There are bad guys looking for that money.
Not yet
Just wait a moment
Just a little bit really
At some point, they made a fuss and asked me to hurry up
Hey there
Are you there?
Why does my mother
Are you this weak?
If you borrowed money
Don't you have to pay it back, huh?
Don't you think you have to pay it back?
Hey, check out if you have any money.
- Where are you?
-Where are you?
Hey, gently so as not to break
Look gently, gently, huh?
Yeah, yeah, hey, gently
Hehe, bastard, uh, uh, uh...
Hey, it's going to be all over the neighborhood.
I can't pay the money back
yellow, sunflower, human
yellow, yellow
Black in the middle, huh?
-Are you colorblind?
- Hello, ma’am.
I'm on the SIU team
It is said to be the strongest
Ah, yes
It's nothing but something
I came because I have something to guide you.
I guess I'll just sit here.
From now on, listen to me carefully.
When inheritance begins
The heir also covers the debts of the deceased.
Because I will inherit it
Relinquish inheritance to the court
However, all heirs
You have to give up
If you give up your inheritance
Can’t I also receive death insurance money?
That's not it
Even if you renounce the inheritance of the death benefit
not an inheritance
Because it is the sole property of the heir.
I can receive it
If a loan shark comes
Even if I tell you to pay off your debt
Just ignore it
What does that guy say, huh?
Hey, is he insured? uh?
I guess so, brother.
Please keep my words in mind.
Please do so
Did you know?
yes, thank you
Are you Soyul?
Wow, you look pretty
Now
Go and eat with mom
Delicious ice cream
Don't give it to your brother, just eat it for yourself.
Okay?
yes, thank you
Beautiful, beautiful
Mr. Really
Go and have a meal
Ah, yes
Talk to me for a moment
Because I'm doing it
Don't worry and go
Uncle, please buy some ice cream too.
It's so twisted! Okay?
Hey, insurance
you come here
Come to someone else’s business
Why are you acting like a loser, you bastard?
Come here, you bastard.
Let's not kill
Hey, do you want to search?
Brother cub is talking
Did you write it all down?
yes
Dining table 3 million won
Chair 2 million won
Oh, what kind of chair?
2 million won each...
Shouldn't it be changed to a set?
It's not a good match
The chair was fine...
yes
And next, table 1 million won
Isn’t this a rip-off?
That's right, a rip off.
Why is it so cheap?
No, yes
Boy, put the cigarette on the table...
Less, cleaning fee: 500,000 won
Yes? Cheong, cleaning...
Based on move-in cleaning fee, huh?
Write it down quickly
yes
I wish I wrote it all down
date, name
Write down your cell phone number and sign
Give it to me
yes
Total 6.5 million won
Right?
yes
Hey, here it is.
Dry spend 7,000 won more
De, de...
Oh, that's not it
I'm going to pay for the dryer now, yeah.
Just a moment...
Here it is
Hey
Because I'm not a bully like you guys
You will only receive the legal maximum interest rate of 20%.
Pay back well
yes
A call is coming
That's my number, huh?
- Yes
- Don't avoid it.
Account information via text message
Yes, please come in...
I'll go after organizing it.
Go in, yeah
Yes, please come in, mother.
- Special attack!
Uh, okay, see you tomorrow!
Doyeon shows off her strength!
Yap, yap, yap, yap!
oh!
Doyeon!
dad!
Did Doyeon’s father come?
yes
Oh my, you’re a cool director today too.
hello
Doyeon, let’s say hello and let’s go quickly.
Special attack!
See you tomorrow, Doyeon.
Me, I guess
I think it will take some time
Ah, yes
Ah, in that brief moment
They even changed the login flow...
He's a complete player
Ah, yes
- Well, I only trust the director.
- Yes
Me too, me too
There's a lot I don't know
I'm in the process of looking for it.
- Yes
- Come in, father.
Doyeon, hello
hello there
hello uncle
Oh, it's Doyeon.
- How are you?
- Yes
Nothing bad, right?
Dad, what's the big deal?
Yeah, I'm just saying, how are you?
Ah
Is everything okay, little brother?
Nothing's wrong with me
friend
Let's say hello to the man and let's go
hello uncle
Yeah, be careful.
- Yes
Not yet
I was just about to tell you that part.
Due to this accident
Now, build a control system and
There may be any danger
Intelligent notification in advance...
Speech Academy Danina, Mr.
Just keep your mouth alive
And again
What happened recently in Giyun City
Unsavory things happen
yes, all the way
Responsibility...
Let's get off work
hello
uh, good morning
Let's leave in 3 minutes
Okay
crazy guy
I live hard
in the morning
I have quite a few delivery reservations.
- I wrote it down on the counter.
- Okay.
Give me a civil servant
Because it will come soon
- Pack some things in advance.
- Okay, okay.
Daughter, did you have a good time at school?
yes
no
Your daughter hasn't even eaten breakfast right now
You feel so bad right now.
They say I won’t buy you sneakers
Don't you smell something acrid?
What are you burning now?
Anyway, you have to be careful driving
Don't just follow your temper
What nature?
uh? What did I just say?
Have a nice trip
If your grade improves on the next midterm exam,
I'll buy you those crazy sneakers
Really?
Is it true?
Is it true, Mom?
Really, then what?
Did you see your mom talking nonsense?
Don't hate it
Wow!
Hey, hey, the car shakes
Wow, really, is it that good?
Oh, I love it.
Mom, tell me again just one more time
Let me record it
What are you doing?
Oh, just once
Whenever I don't want to study
I want to listen
Oh my, really
Minseo Kim
It's mom
If your grade goes up during the next midterm exam,
Those crazy sneakers worth 500,000 won
Mom will buy it for you
But if your grades drop
you don't even have soup
promise
Did something happen?
Mom, there's a fire truck over there.
It’s the last stop of the village bus, right?
Um, is that the burnt smell from earlier?
No, but what accident happened?
Why are you blocking it like this?
- How is the patient's condition?
- No consciousness
Are you unconscious?
be careful
Uh, high-ranking executives in Changni-dong.
Are you all gathered here?
Oh, I guess they're leaving now?
yes
Were you in a serious meeting?
Don't even talk
The bus exploded and there was chaos right now.
Yes?
No, at the last stop of the village bus
The bus exploded
No one got hurt?
Oh, I don't know.
We’re frustrated too.
There is no one telling me
It's not even on the news
Uh, right, yeah
Because Do-yeon’s dad works at an insurance company.
I understand.
No, after an accident like this
Who usually comes to the scene first?
What if it's a big accident?
police, ambulance, fire truck
Even insurance companies like us come.
Look, look, this is normal
No, why is the soldier here?
Are you a soldier?
in the morning
While taking my daughter to school
I took a peek
Because there was a military car
Yes, brother
No, the Joint Chiefs of Staff and the first car came.
The Joint Chiefs of Staff and No. 1 car?
uh
Huh? What do you mean?
Uh, hey, there's a friend of mine, uh.
No, Minseo’s tutor.
no, no
Hey, let me call you.
I have your number
I understand
Don't cry, just wait
yes
- This deacon?
- Yes
Why, what?
No, there
Myeong-oh went to work.
They said they couldn't contact me
He said he left early to take the first train.
Hey, what's wrong? uh?
yes, teacher
Yes, this is Minseo’s mom.
Hey, maybe today
Have you contacted Myeongo?
There was an accident
In it...
Mother!
119, 119, 119
- In a patrol car...
- I'll carry you!
Ah, teacher
Sister, sister, come to your senses
So
When there is a traffic accident at an intersection
A soldier came and cleaned it up.
When the ATM exploded
The firefighter was wearing military boots
When the village bus exploded
It means that the Joint Chiefs of Staff and the first car have arrived.
- That's right.
-Mr...
All three are bombs
Even in car accidents
They said there was gray smoke coming from the car.
Brother Soo-il
I remember it clearly
It was like that when the ATM accident happened.
Chunbae said he saw it this morning.
gray smoke
C4
Looks like C4
Of course, it could be a deformed bomb, but
Is it ours again?
Are you sure?
Anna, I'm going crazy, really, Mr.
Are you inside?
hang up
Why aren't you answering the phone, so annoying!
Oh, did you call?
Oh my
You made a lot of calls.
Thanks to you like this
It's nice to see your face
Are you kidding?
The village bus exploded
Two people died
One is in intensive care
Don't you lower your voice?
Here
Is this the main room of your house? Tsk
No, I mean the kids outside
It's not good if you listen to it.
sit
What kind of shit did you do?
Are you bursting with laughter as the day goes by?
Why is that our Kiyun City again?
Already in the IT special tourist zone
Sullivan's is missing.
People are going crazy
I can't help you!
Do you guys understand? uh?
Hey, I'm dying from a headache too.
I have to clean up after myself, with the speculum police in control.
Hey, with the press...
I haven't been able to go to the sauna for a few days now.
You, you know? I have a bad shoulder
I was tortured, oh oil, old...
Handles work like a fool
Your mouth is so heavy, isn’t it?
Everyone doesn't say anything!
What on earth is going on?
You asked
you go forward
A person who does great work for the country
You, Mr. Huh?
What is a double body? This idiot, Mr.
you
You were on the same boat with me anyway, huh?
I also went to Giyun City Special Tourist Zone.
Because I didn't know anything
So now I'm just like, huh?
Diligently before you get sick
I'm not sweeping and wiping
What on earth is going on?
I don’t know, neither do I!
I'm learning!
Minister
You really don’t know, right?
This is anyway
It's a problem I have to deal with, right?
I'll take care of it.
So please stop fucking
Can we go for a bit?
If you mess around behind my back, I will kill you by my hands.
Wow, just leave that shallow bitch alone.
With a single gun, just, bang, Mr.
Wow, Mr.
They say people live up to their names
Even you, Ozzy, are the best in Korea.
A person with no face to face
Going to the funeral
Hardware store, supermarket, laundromat
I knew everything well
my friend's friend
He's a friend to me too
How can you pretend not to know?
He is the only son of a single mother.
Graduated from Korea University
Working part-time for 3 years
While preparing for a job
He said he got hired by a large company this time.
I'm going to work for the first time
I got arrested while riding the bus.
Anyone who sees me will think I'm your best friend.
I even said this
I wasn't going to do it
Best friend's best friend's best friend
Best friend to me too
Because you are my forever best friend
- In times like this...
-Noisy and
Relief is moderate
Let's not overdo it.
Yes, ma'am
don't go outside
I'm at home with Doyeon.
If you have anything to order
Order everything from me, okay?
- As usual
- Oh, go quickly, go.
I heard it a little bit earlier
Well, did you get permission to go there?
Oh, I need permission.
Then, of course
Oh, really?
Hey, Su-il’s brother.
I saw you being held captive by your sister-in-law.
I thought it was so pitiful
Hey, here's an extra eight pennies.
Since you got caught, they're giving you something to live with.
Even the funeral is permitted.
Does that fit it?
I'm being caught.
It doesn't look like that
You're sharper than you think, huh?
But why did the reporters come?
Well, it was an accident, so we’re going to cover the bereaved family?
What do reporters do?
I'm not doing any reporting.
I guess someone high up came, or something.
let's go
It's here!
The acting increases every day, I
Come on, let's go.
I will meet you first and tell you.
Rep.
How extensive is the damage?
this incident
How many victims?
Just one word
Please!
Mother
You have to cheer up.
I
I can't live
my son...
without a son
I can't live
Rep., please help us.
Myeong-oh, please save me.
Myeong-oh, take your mom with you too.
Take your mom too!
mother
Myeong-oh's unfair death
I will definitely find out
thank you
Our Myeong-oh...
Ah...
What should I do about the store and come here?
Yes, close the door for a moment
I brought Chunbae brother with me.
Let's shift at night
I couldn't stand Gosae
Boy, this is really mean, really.
My neighbor's cousin died
People say they can't do business for a few days...
Who does it for money?
A good supermarket in the neighborhood
There is only one
I came here to buy urgent groceries.
Gongchi is afraid that there will be guests.
Hurry up and eat
Oh, right, I have no appetite.
Ah...
Why do you keep selling me?
I came separately
You have no loyalty
You don't have any sense, huh?
Let’s eat beef jerky.
Today
I think it's almost finished
come here and eat
I haven't eaten all day
I'm fine
Myeong-oh’s mother is now
The person I rely on the most is my teacher.
What if we fall together?
Eat some
quickly
Oh my, is Yonghee here?
Yes, sister
I was late because I finished painting.
yes
Say hello to Myung-oh
Wow, myeonghyo
Oh, what should I do, oh
You didn’t eat, right?
Oh, I ate it, sister.
Please sit down
Ah, here
Minseo's tutor
Myeongo’s friend, Myeongo introduced me.
And here
Special martial arts dojo director
Myeong-oh and I are close friends from the neighborhood.
My name is Park Jeong-hwan.
Yes, this is Yonghee Lee.
Are you heartbroken?
yes
Sister
Oh my, I still can't believe it.
We're all like that, right?
Myeong-oh's mother
Myeong-oh came to work wearing a suit
'I've been there'
They say I'm coming to the funeral home
Ah, our Myeong-oh
I want to see you in a suit.
Oh no
I...
Ah, myeong-one, ayu
- Oh, what should I do?
- Wow
Wear a nice suit
I wore a tie and went to work.
Our Myeong-oh
So, oh
Oh, can I get you something?
I need to go to the bathroom for a second...
yes
who is holding the event
I brought you a doll.
It's a video
People who receive the event from the morning
I wish it so much
What's wrong, Yonghee?
Uh, sister, let me go first...
Oh my, why is he like that?
older brother!
why?
Hey, there's a rabbit, rabbit.
- What's wrong?
- yes? That...
A rabbit caught a bus, bro!
What are you talking about, you bastard?
Aren't you coming to your senses?
Why is there a bus on the rabbit...
- Rabbit?
- Oh, yes!
So, yeah
on the bus seat
There was a rabbit doll, brother!
How did you know that?
Myeong-oh took the picture, Myeong-oh took it
- Hey, can you see that?
- Yes
Really? Look, look, look
Where are you looking?
Where?
- Private
- uh?
What, where are you?
So, over there, Myeong, Myeong-o and
I can't do that...
Hey Lee, hurry up
Where, where are you? Quick...
How did you see it earlier?
There before
At the funeral...
To my friend...
Hey, that...
Uh, hey, what I saw earlier.
Will I see you again?
Uh, here, this is the doll, right?
So
Even the dolls in the villa
It smelled sweet and greasy.
Yes? What do you mean?
C4
Yes?
A bomb?
What does that mean?
Just now
You left after looking at the photos.
What is this?
Uh, this, that...
please tell me in detail
It's my friend's business.
on the bus
I think there was a bomb.
Who on earth does that?
Who does that?
This is dangerous, so let's take care of it...
no
Me too
who is that bastard
By all means
I want to find out
Uh, okay, okay.
Raise it a little, raise it a little
Thank you for your hard work in the hot weather.
Please take care of me, yeah
I am a person who keeps promises.
Changni-dong residents
So you can live safely
Intelligent AI CCTV
Installing
Are you worried?
Sure
In our Changni-dong
How can something like this happen one after another?
Now this kind of thinking
I will make sure it never happens again.
thank you
This is school
It will also be installed in front of the kids’ school, right?
Wow, I lost my cow.
I fix the barn noisily.
Baby, I can hear it all
Oh, listen or not
Oh, I wish I could hear it
There's that
They're saying they're going to use that to spy on us.
Huh?
Hey, but what should I do, huh?
The strongest no comment in the world
I can't avoid that.
Right? uh
Should I bet?
Can I avoid that or can’t I avoid it?
oh
500 won for ‘I Can’t Avoid’
My younger brother bets on ‘avoiding’
Just stay here, okay?
I brought a real gun
I'm really about to shoot you, really, sir.
I'm so gullible
What?
My younger brother has fun teasing me
don't do it
Don't do it
Ha, Mr.
I really don't know what to do
Won't you stop? Just...
Bring the gun, Mr.
It's online CCTV, it's unfortunate
Why can't you avoid that?
That's not it
If that's online
Even the satellite computer
I do it because I think you might be watching.
What would your brother know?
Ah, so what, what should I do?
The rhythm has to match
Man, this guy is really crazy.
Because the crazy one is over there, not me, right?
one
two
three
Hey, and one, two
- Three! eat, seed
- Eat, yes, you bastard.
Eat, eat
- Eat.
- Eat, eat, eat, eat
Eat it with a fastball
eat
Hey, let’s feed him something big.
one, two, three
Come in
Hey!
Giyun City explodes
I think there's a connection.
Reporting to me
What is the reason?
I was in room 203
I brought something with me
Computer signal
Because it was cut off at the police box
They will come there
While crowding around
What are they planning?
People in the neighborhood are dying
You don't have to do anything
Ah!
A warning of a bombing in Giyun City?
- Get out of the way
- Immediately arrest him and investigate.
Who are you?
How did you know about this place?
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri